What moment was it for you in your life
and ultimately why did you make the decision to
pursue the entrepreneur route as opposed to
playing it safe, maybe getting a comfortable
six-figure job in the corporate world? What kind
of clicked in you that you were like,
this is what I ought to do? I had too
many people to provide for and I had too much
people that were depending on me. I
think most people shouldn't start a business personally.
If you look at the numbers, it's 86% of
companies in the United States break even or lose money.
One half of 1% of our revenue is over
$10 million. So if you actually line up what
business owners actually make versus an employee,
net revenue on average is actually the employee
makes about $3,000 to $4,000 more.
I think it's like 58 to 55.